Nick: Hi there. I’m Nick.
Expert: Hi, Nick.
So what’s your problem?
Nick: Well, I’ve been with my girlfriend for three years.
We have a really great relationship although we’re quite different.
She’s clever and popular,
and I’m, er, quiet and hard-working.
Anyway, now she wants to move to London because she thinks she can get a better job there,
and she wants me to go to London, too – you know,
London’s much more exciting than Bolton, where we live now.
But I have a good job in Bolton and I get a good salary.
I mean, the idea of moving and having a new life is like a dream, but
for me that’s what it is – I mean,
it’s a dream, it isn’t real.
What should I do?
Should I follow my heart and move to London with her?
Or should I stay here, where I know I have a good job, but possibly lose my girlfriend?